morning everyone welcome to
Chris's Hong Kong the sale
that we have been waiting for this season The Tam
collection we begin this morning with
lot 2701 is the fine mag magnificent
exceptionally rare blue and
white peony squirrel Ming and
cover and starting here at 17 million I start
here at 17 million at 17 million looking for
18 Place 18 18 one at 18 19 million I have now
18 20 million I have already on the telephone
here the side 20 22 million back here at 22
million in the room head of the phones at
22 million with you at 22 million who give me
24 or higher 22 million at 22 million holding
here at 224 now is that a bit 24 with 8 at 24
million 26 million back here in the room at
26 at 26 million bus here in the room ahead of
the telephones at 26 give me 28 please or higher
it's a 26 28 million 30 million much better
at 30 million on the film 32 back here at 3
32 million head of the F give me 35 35 million
wor Rebecca at 38 million back here in the room
at 38 at 38 million Rebecca give me 40 or
anyone else at 38 million still with you
40 million with Rebecca at 42 back here in the
room now at 42 million still going on here at
42 give me 45 higher at 42 million holding here
at 42 million Rebecca and everyone else at 42
million still with you 42 million at 42 million
42 million holding here who's coming next 42
million holding there 42 Rebecca give me 45
CH a f at 42 million still with you sir at
42 45 million back to Rebecca now 45 and good
morning Mr chair 45 million Rebecca has the B
right now 48 45 at 45 million holding with
Rebecca at 45 45 million Rebecca has a bit
at 45 million head of seated ahead of the F the
side at 45 million 48 million CH joins us now at
48 48 million have 50 or
higher at 48 million with Gund
Rebecca 48 million with Chan 50 million
Rebecca took it back at 50 take it back
Chan at 50 million with Rebecca at
50 million1 Rebecca 50 million give
me 55 at 50 million with Rebecca
at 50 million 50 million give me
55 50 million coming in it's a 50 million
holding with Rebecca at the moment at 50
50 million 55 million 51 million for
51 51 million can I have 52 from you
ohca 51 million holding that with ch CL at 51 51
million are you still bu sir 51 million Rebecca
one holding what you 52 million in the room at 52
million gentleman's bit up front at 52 now ahead
of the fil 52 million 52 million holding here
up front Jan Rebecca give me 53 52 million 52
Milli 53 million with back up
back to her phone at 53 by one 53
53 million holding with Rebecca at the moment at
53 53 million
yes what do you think
so 54 back now at
54 54 million holding what
you find at the moment give me
55 don't let it go so easily at 54
million 54 million any for the Rebecca
talk to your client where's your bidding
down 54 million Chief and Hazard heard
of you seated heard of the on there feed
on trading man 54 million extremely rare
with cover very good condition remarkable
blue you won't see it again for
a while a 54 million which CH
fan 54 million waiting for
you Chan has the bid firmly on
her phone 55 million back in the
room here 55 55 keep on going here with you sir
Rebecca down 55 million back
in the room you almost had
it try one more you can do it at
55 million J is really trying I
can tell 55 million yes that's
a bit 56 million back to Chan's
Fone 56 about what 56 million which Chan
head of Rebecca head of us give me one
more 56 million with Chan again
and ahead of you sir at 56
million 56 million which you
give you a bit pressure just
a little bit 56 million hold in there very
sure you're very sure G us up and
selling at 56 million l so for 56
million 8011 congratulations well
done and thank you very much for
bidding and move on to lot 2702
is the important extremely rare
blue and why molded Bob Rim charger from the
dynasty and open here at 14 million I open at
14 15 million with Angela she has a bit of 15
million now I'm looking for 16 please at have 15
million with Angela can I have 16 16 with aah now
at 16 million adah has a bit come back to me for
17 please Angela at 60 million with at 60 million
holding at 6 million with a at the moment give
me 17 please 16 me 17 million back to Angel 17
million a give me 18 17 million holding
with Angela give me 18 please 17 million
Angela 17 million holding with Angela
17 million 18 18 18 million back to
ad now at 18 million give me 19 19 million
Angela took it back at 19 give me 20 at 19
million 19 million holding with Angela give me
20 20 please anywhere else and 19 million holding
with Angela 20 million bid with aah she took it
back at 20 million give me 22 please at 20 million
with 21 21 million with Angela at 21 million we
going one now give me 22 at 21
million holding with Angela 21
million 21 million holding there with Angela
ahead of aead of the room he give me 20 any
forance over 21 million at 21 million then with
Angela ad still biding at 21 million then Angela
has the bid for the re charger at 21 million
any furthers over 21 million CH trying to come
in now will be a chance at 21 million Angel has
to B head of v head of chund for 21 million now
have your chance talk to your client yes
or no hopefully it's a yes at 21 million
give you pressure here at 21 million still holding
there with Angela thank you for your patience she
find very sure thank you for trying 21 million
then Angela has this and I'm selling to Angela
client unless there's a high bit over 21 million
selling and S 21 million well done Angela 8010
congratulations thank you Kevin
273 is the fin manificent blue
and white grapes bar Rim charger from the
period and for this classic example open here
at 6,500,000 I start here 6 million5 one C by
one 7 million I have now 7,500,000 7 million5
I have in the room give me 8 million please
at 7,500,000 gentlemen seated here has it
at 7 million5 8 million with Marco he has
a been now 88 million 8 million5 back in the
room 8 million5 give me 9 8 million 500,000 9
million back to Marco and 9 million 500,000 in
the room here give me 10 please and 9,500,000
holding here in the room 10 million worth Marco
now would you like 11 11 million in the room 11
million is been Now give me 12 please at 11 12
million back to Marco 13 million back here at 13
million take you back for 14 please at 30 million
holding here in the room at 30 million e stand by
with f now I 14 what I 15 15 million back in the
room I 15 million heard of the film give me 16
Place 15 million F give me 16 please 16
million I saw fa 16 million 16 million
now 17 million 17 million 17 Milli 1 million
here in the room I have 70 million 18 million
with Isaac I saw Isaac first pH like try if
you like at 19 million I still have the room
there ahead of the phone at 19 give me 20
at 20 million F has it at 20 million would
you like 22 22 at 20 million with very ahead
of the room at 20 million which like 22 or F
like it's 20 pardon it's a 22 million
with Felix now at 22 million he has a
bit at 22 million who give me 24 Felix has
a bit at 22 Isaac coming for 24 22 million
million with ph head of f head of head
of at 22 million any for the fs over
22ac sure at 22 million then Felix has a bit F CH
at 22 million of which all through now
be chance never at 22 million then I'm
selling to Phil client for 22 million
last so 22 million for you Felix 8019
congratulations 2704 is the exceedingly
rare and outstanding blue and white
ladings in Garden ball from the per
period and open here at 12 million at 12 million
at 12 million at 12 million at 12 million holding
here at 12 million who give me 13 13 million I
have die die just ahead of 14 million with Jasmine
now I 14 I have 14 with jasine said Jasmine's
bit at 14 million give me 15 please at 14 million
with Jasmine head of you at 14 million any for
the 15 million with now at 15 million she has
a million give me 16 please at 15
million worth a it's a 15 million
worth a at the moment at 15 give
me 16 if you like 15 million has a
bit 15 million head of the side head of
the other two telephones at 15 million
jine at 15 million hasard 15 million very sure
at 15 million then ad Haz it head of the other
telephones for 15 million very sure and L and
selling them at 15 million so at 15 million 8025
congratulations 2705 is the very rare
exceptional blue and white dragon dish
from the period Mar period here extremely rare
example of Blue from the period and open here
at 2 million 2,200,000 at 2 Milli I have Tim
here at 2 million 400,000 Tim has a bit at 2
million6 now I have Melody ahead of your 2
million 8 back to Tim at 2 million 8 Melody
give me three please at 2,800,000 3 million
Jasmine joins us now 3 million2 back to Tim
at 3 million2 at 3 Mill 2 3 million 5 in the
room here at 3 million 5 head of the phones at 3
million5 3 Milli 5
still 3 800,000 with J 4 million back in the room
4 million give me 4 two please 4 million 4 million
give me 4 two Jasmine Tim Melody like 42 4 million
4 million it's a four million in the room with
you million very sure 4 million for this very red
dish are you bding sir at 4,200,000 4,200,000 new
place 4 3
now 4 400
which like 4 million6 4,500,000
4, 600,000 thank you at 4
million6 at 4, 600,000 you have this
head if you seated half of the F for 4,
600,000 our way all through at 4, 600,000 at 4,
600,000 then G up and selling
at 4, 600,000 so for 4,6 9387
congratulations 2706 is the impressive and finally
painted large Blue and y4 scholarly
Pursuit jar from the juding period
and here 800,000 850,000 900,000 is
Bid already 900,000 900,000 1 milon
at 1 million bid here with me give me one
one please at 1 million holding here where
is 1,100,000 1 million1 1,200,000 back here
give me 1 three please and 1,200,000 holding
here 1 million2 1 million3 p has a been now
at 1,300,000 head of the other telephones
at 1 million 3 1 million4 at 1 million4 with
mending now at 1 milon 4 give me 1 million5
please and 1 million5 back to PO at 1 million5
at 1,500,000 po has a bid at 1 million5 who
where is 1 mil6 at 1,500,000 po has the bit
heard of the other telephones at 1,500,000
at 1,500,000 with polar head of the phones
at 1,500,000 polar has it meny how 1,500,000
heard of the phones at 1,500,000 then
polar has it yes or no Mendy is that
a bit waiting for you 1,500,000 still with
polar and I'm selling unless there's a higher
bit over 1,500,000 J are you still
bidding give me a signal if you are
1,600,000 J took it back polar try
1 Milli 7 please at 1,600,000 J has
a bid now at 1 mil6 1,700,000 back to
Polar give me one eight please 1,700,000
with 1,700,000 still holding that
with po give one more bid 1,700,000
thank you very much Jay for bidding
still with polar 1,700,000 ahead of
the phones ahead of the room at 1,700,000
and selling at 1 mil7 so 1,700,000 8020
congratulations 2707 is the rare and
finely painted one Le Mark period do
high fruit and flower ball one do
and open here at 700,000 750,000
750 at 750,000 it's with me here at
750,000 850,000 holding here
950,000
holding 1,00,000 with my commission
B 1,200,000 1,200,000 with you
are you bidding 1,200,000 in
the room front row P number one
hasard at 1 million2 1,200,000
1,200,000 holding here up
front 1,300,000 B is online now at 1
mil3
1 mil back in the room here
head online at 1,400,000
1,400,000 one more you online
at 1,400,000 1 mil5 back
to 1,500,000 then on Chris's
life head of the room if
1,500,000 Chris life Hazard ahead
of the room ahead of the phone at
1,500,000 our we all through gevels
up and selling at 1,500,000 so to
you on Chris live 1 million 53014
congratulations and thank you for
bidding 278 is the very rare blue
and whitean dish one per and open
here at 600,000 600,000 I'm looking for 650
please 600,000 600,000 who's coming in for 650 at
600,000 holding here look into online
look into the room who give me 650
you 600,000 holding here 600,000 any for
the 600,000 any for the fs over
600,000 600,000 any for the fs on the
telephone in the room on Chris life at
600,000 fair warning and no
regrets pass at 600,000 and we
move on to lot 2709 is the very
rare blue and white and iron red molded Lotus dis
period here again 600,000
600,000 looking for 650 please at
600,000 600,000 600,000 what do you
think sir 600,000 now be chance at
600,000 look into the room looking online at
600,000 at 600,000 very sure rub
bidding at 600,000 not for this L
try that next one then at 600,000 fair warning at
600,000 pass at 600,000 and move on to 2710 is the
fine and exceedingly rare large
blue and white floral squirel Bas
period and open here at 4,500,000 I
start here at 4 mil5 4,500,000 for over
4500000 4,500,000 4 million5 M are coming in
4,500,000 heard of you there 4 mil5 4,500,000
any over 4 million5 4,500,000 are we all
through then very sure at 4,500,000 any
for f l faing and no regrets pass formula
five and we move on to lot 2711 is the fine
magnificent exceedingly rare y Mark and period
blue and white flowers off the Four Season Moon
flask and open here at 12 million I start here at
12 million 12 mil3 I have here in the room 13 I
have where is the next B at 13 million is with you
sir at 1 13 million I'm looking for 14 place at
13 14 million B is up here in the front give me
15 15 million on my right is that a bit
15 million 15 Milli 15 million now 15
million 15 milon holding
there 50 million coming on the
telephone 15 million with you sir 15 million
50 million holding there 15 million at 15 at
1550 million I will need to see your high value
P please 15 million at 15 million now 16 million
with Victoria as Victoria she has a been now
at 16 million 16 million at 16 million at 16
million I have to see a high value P for this
placee at 16 million each 10 little one Victoria
the at 160 million 60 million holding there
at 16 million Victoria has a head of the F
this side at 6 million are you coming in 16
million with Victoria it's with you at the
moment million which 1 million Milli
has it you there you seated here at
17 million million Victoria 1 million
holding which 17 million she has a b 17
million 1
million 17 mil 500,000 with Victoria give me 18
please at 1,500,000 with Victoria take it back for
18 Place 7,500,000 Victoria has a b 17 million5
Victoria has a bit give me 18 please 17 mil
500,000 1,500,000 18 million which Chief F
now I have 18 million Chief took it back for
18 one give me 18 million5 or higher it's 18
million Chief has a b 18 million 18 million
18, 500,000 back to Victoria just ahead of
your Chief 18 million5 Victoria has a bid at
18 million5 Chief find give me the next bid
please at 18, 500,000 Victoria has it at 18
mil5 with Victoria how do you see
it here 18, 500,000 give me 19
please 18 million5 are you
bidding Victor run up to 19 19 million of course
which van 19,500 th000 and 19 mil 500,000 is
Bid in the room here at 19 million5 in the room
now ahead of the phone at 19 mil 500,000 19 mil
500,000 20 million bid now on the telephone at 22
at 22 21 million in the room here at 21 million at
21 just ahead of the phone there at 21 Milli many
places still who will give me the next bid it's a
21 it's a 21 million in the room here at
21 head the side head of the phone at 21
million Rebecca are you bidding at 21 million
holding there with you sir at 21 million 21,
500,000 Chief F Hazard first just ahead of you
by one second give me 22 please 22 million back
to Victoria 22 million one Victoria has it
at 22 million 22 million which like 22 milon
500,000 22 million 22 mil 500,000 I
like your signal at 22 mil 500,000
23 million back to Victoria 23 23 million
23 million with Victoria Chief and take
it back give me another 500,000 at
23 million holding there at 23 23
million 23 23 million 500,000 back to
Chan at 23 million5 give him 24 please
at 2 3,500,000 24 back to Victoria
24 give me another 500,000 please
at 24 million with Victoria on my right
here at 24 million Chan Don't Let It Go
24 million holding there with Victoria give
me another 500,000 24, 500,000 back to CH 24
mil5 24, 500,000 holding what CH there 25 million
thank you Victoria she has a bit 25 million Chan
Don't Let It Go a 25 million 25 million Victoria
has it head if you seated here she still has a bid
at 25 million give me another 500,000 please at 25
million holding that 25 million still withth your
Victoria 25 million any further of us
at 25 million you're waving sir at 25
million you're waving indeed 25 million still with
Victoria 2,500,000 which shean she took a back
at 2,500,000 which shean Victoria take it back
26 million and you have it there 26 million
26 million back to Victoria Chan 26 million
26 million 26 million with Victoria Marco I
love your smile a 26 million Chan don't give
up love your smile she's trying talk to your
client 26 mil 500,000 26 mil5 Victoria very
sure at 26,500 th000 with Chan Victoria
Fair trading came such a long way very
short please thank your client 26,500
th000 then wian head Victoria there we
all through at 26,500 th000 then last selling
and sold for you 26,500 a011 congratulations
2712 is a final superb clear
delom glaze con V CH Mark
period and an open here at 1,700,000 I start here
1,7 1 million 8 at 1,800,000 1 million 9 ahead of
your 2 million is B at 2 million 2 million2 2
million2 is B here up front in the room at 2
million2 give me two4 please at 2 million2
2 million4 I saw J first can you give me 2
million6 at 2,400,000 is with j at the moment
2 million6 back in the room here at 2 million6
many places still at 2 million6 at who give
me 2 million 8 or higher at 2,600,000 holding
here where reason now 28 give me 3 million
please at 2,800,000 where is my next b 2
Milli one can I have 3 million please
we still have many places here 3 million
is where was the bed 3 million of
course 3 million how silly of Me 3
million is up here up front first show
3 million has it at 3 million ahead of
the other BS at 3 million can I have
3 million please 3 million 3,200,000
wish 3 mil5 is B here at 3
million5 give me 38 3,500,000
one 3,500,000 now will be your chance at 3,500,000
holding here up front head
of the phones are we all
through 3,500,000 holding here are we all through
all done then G up and selling a 3,500,000 for
you sir 3,500,000 p number one thank you very
much for showing me your paddle in D number one
congratulations thank you lot 2713 is the F
and exceptionally rare seladon
glaze qu dragon v from the CH
here for this beautiful v i open
here at 9,500,000 I open at 9 mil5
by E1 at 9,500,000 holding here
9 million5 10 million B with at
10 million1 at 10 million where is 11
million 11 million with Angela at 11
million at 11 million holding with
Angela there at 11 million that give
me 12 12 million a half now at 12 million at
13 million a half with Angela 1 million can
I 14 1 million holding there 1 million
Angela has a bit at the moment ahead
of at 13 million holding there with you
at 13 million at 13 million holding there
yes or no look at me are you bidding
at 13 million Angela has it ahead of
the other films and ahead of them at
13 million holding at the moment who
else would like to join us here for
this Exquisite ass at 13 million it's
are you coming in at 13 million 14 million hasn't
been now at 14 at 14 million Angela like 15 at
15 million back to Angela at 15 Chan give me 16
please at 15 million Angela has it at 15 million
16 15 million with Angela at the moment head
of the room head of D 15 million give me 16 15
million
60 million with 60 million 70 million back to
Angel 70 million Chief don't thr bid please at
70 million with Angela give me the next bit
at 70 million with Angela 1 million any for
the vs from this side is a 170 million
do you want try 18 please 17 million 18
million back to 18 million 18 million give
me 19 please Angela and 19 million Angela
has it no you sure very sure 18 million with
Chan letting this go 18 ahead of Angela very
certain has a Bed Head of Angela head of D
head of the room at 18 million any further
FS over 18 million it's 18 million then 18
million very sure lot on SC up and selling
at 18 18 million so foran 18 million 8011
congratulations and thank you Angela and D for
bidding lot 2714 is a superbly painted blue and
white flower and fruit spray May paint CH Mark and
[Music] period 3,500,000 I start here
at 3,500,000 who Me 3 mil8 at 3 mil5 3,
800,000 now at 3 looking for four
please can you give me four at 3,
800,000 at 3, 800,000 is not yours yet
give me four please if you wish at 3,
800,000 try four 4 million I have Jasmine now
at 4 million she has a bid from the Ming at
4 million one Chief train for the slot at
4 million Jasmine's bid head of the other
biders here at 4 million Jasmine has it four
Chief give me 4 to or higher please Jasmine
has it 4 million any 4,200,000 back to Chan at
4 milon2 Jasmine give me 45 4,200,000 holding
with Chan at the moment 4 five back to Jasmine
and 4 five 48 please 4,500,000 with Jasmine 4
million5 45 4 800,000 back to 48 4 800,000
J take it back for five 5 million with Jas
a 5 million give me 5 million five Chan a
5 million with Jasmine you had a moment ago
Chan at 5 million 5 Milli 500,000 back
to Chan at 5 million5 give me six at
5 5,500,000 Hing with chief fan head
of jasine very sure build with chief
fan again at 5,500,000 head of Jasmine head of the
room 5,2 00,000 what the bit Jasmine now you
have the chance to have 5,500,000 would you
like to try that it's a 5,200,000 which she
find 5 million2 try you never know might be
yours at 5,200,000 which you find 300,000
more 5 million2 give it a try 5,200,000
anyone else would like to join us here 5
milon2 Jasmine talk to your C very sure
5,200,000 then with Chan thank you for
trying at 5,200,000 Chan has a bid and
I'm selling unless there's a higher bit
over 5,200,000 L and so 5,200,000 8011
congratulations and 2715 the
final order in today's sale The
Taming law collection sale is the
exceptionally rare Exquisite pair
all blue ground guil decorated melon and
Vine double gold form vases CH Mark and
period and at 12 million open at
12 million by at 12 million open
here looking for 13 13 million with
Angela she has a bit of 13 by1 at
13 million with Angela looking for
14 13 million Angela has a bit at 1
million million holding with Angela
there at 13 million she has a
bit 13 million Angela has a bit
it's a 30 million 1 million with
Angela and a selling bid at 13 million
with Angela Jasmine you're pointing to
that was not a bit but thank
you at 13 million still with
Angela are you coming in 14 million with Victoria
she has been now at 14 million Victoria has it
now at 14 million give me 15 15 back to Angela at
15 million give me 16 1550 million Angela has it
1550 million at the moment give me 16 you sure
you didn't get the last one try this one at 15
million 16 million back to
Victoria here 16 million
million for 18 million back to Victoria
18 million now 18 million Victoria has it
18 19 million with Angela at 19 give me 20
please a 90 million Angela has it a 19 give
me 20 a 20 20 Mill 90 million 21 21 million
we jump two increments with 21 million with
Victoria at 21 million we like that always
22 million at 22 million with Angela at 22
million 22 million try one more or a few more
23 million at 23 million with Victoria at 23
24 back to Angela at 24 give me 25 please 24
million 25 million Victoria at 26 million back
to Angela at 26 million 27 please you very
sure you said no the last 27 million welcome
back again at 27 million at 28 million with
Angela went at 28 2 million back to Ang 29
with Victoria at 29 29 million me 30 million
30 million Angela has it at 30 may have 31
next such a long way don't let it go at 30
million Victoria 31 million 31 mil Victoria
31 31 32 million at 32 32 million 32 million with
Angela talk to your client it's so rare 32
million 32 million 33 million with Victoria
33 million S one 33 33 million S one
Angela are you sure at 33 million gender trading
thank you very much for bidding at 33 million and
seems like Victoria you have the lot at 33 million
ahead of you there Angela very sure are we very
sure all done L's fair warning and I'm selling
at 33 million L and so 33 million 021 [Applause]
congratulations and Ladies and Gentlemen
please stay with with me as we'll reopen lot
2710 4,200,000 4 million2 4,200,000 give me 4 mil5
4,500,000 with Jasmine she has a bit at
4 mil5 4,500,000 I'll we all through at
4,500,000 and over 4 mil5 selling at
4,500,000 so adjustment 4 500,000 a02a
congratulations and I concludes the sale of
the T M low collection thank you very much
for your participation and congratulations
to the buyers and congratulations Tam of
course thank you very much for your trust
and chrises and we'll begin the sale of
the important and Chinese Ceramics and work
of art momentarily I'll see you again very
soon